{"title": "Revit", "questions": [{"question": "Q1. What is it called when a tag with a leader has a drag control where the leader touches the element?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " Attached End\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " Preferences &gt; Reviewing\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Preferences &gt; Reading\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Preferences &gt; Commenting\n</ul>\n<p><a href=\"https://quizlet.com/ie/582293749/revit-skills-flash-cards/#:~:text=30.,Free%20End\">Source</a></p>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q2. A designer would like to create a new parameter in a schedule that contains a mathematical expression combining two existing fields. What is the process?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " <code>Edit Fields &gt; Combined Parameter</code>\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " <code>Sorting/Grouping &gt; Grand Totals</code>\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " <code>Formatting &gt; Field Formatting &gt; Calculate Totals</code>\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " <code>Edit Fields &gt; Calculated Parameter</code>\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q3. Where can you find a drop-down list of available named reference planes?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " in the <strong>Properties</strong> palette\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " in the Project Browser\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " on the Options Bar\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " in the <strong>Set Work Plane</strong> dialog box\n</ul>\n<p><a href=\"https://www.revithq.com/blogs/tips-tricks-tutorials-and-content/reference-planes-drag-controls\">Source</a></p>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q4. Some Revit families require a host element to be placed. Which choice is a hosted element?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " door\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " floor\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " furniture\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " wall\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q5. In what type of view are you <em>unable</em> to create a new level?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " section view\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " elevation view\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " 3D view\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " plan view\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": true}]}, {"question": "Q6. In a model whose units are configured in feet, what would you type to get a liner object to be 100 millimeters long?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " 100'\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " 100/25.4\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " 100mm\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " 100m\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q7. A colleague shared an Excel file with you, and you want to display a worksheet that is hidden in it. How can you do that?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " On the <strong>View</strong> tab, click <strong>New Window</strong>.\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " On the <strong>Review</strong> tab, click <strong>Unhide Sheet</strong>.\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " On the <strong>Home</strong> tab, click <strong>Unhide</strong>.\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Right-click any worksheet tab and select <strong>Unhide</strong>.\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": true}]}, {"question": "Q8. When sketching a roof by footprint, which option allows an edge of the sketch to be sloped in the final roof?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " Slope arrow\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Extend to wall core\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " Defines slope\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Overhang\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q9. When importing a CAD drawing into a drafting view, how do you remove layers that you do not need?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " Select the imported CAD drawing, click the Query tool, and then in the dialog that appears, click <strong>Delete</strong>.\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " Select the imported CAD drawing and, on the <strong>Properties</strong> palette, click <strong>Edit Type</strong> &gt; <strong>Delete Layers</strong>.\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Select the improted CAD drawing, tab to select elements you don't want, and then press Delete.\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Select the imported CAD drawing, right-click, and select <strong>Delete Layers</strong>.\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q10. When working with design option, what <em>cannot</em> be placed in the option sets?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " hosted components\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " in-place models\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " detail items\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " system families\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q11. In a legend view, where would you find the drop-down list of the families - such as doors, windows, and other components - you want to use as legend components?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " contextual <strong>Modify</strong> tab on the ribbon\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Options Bar\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " right-click menu\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Type Selector\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q12. While working in Revit, you often need additional lines to help define locations for elements in a mode. You can hide these lines in the appropriate views later, when necessary. What are these extra lines called?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " detail lines\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " construction lines\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " reference planes\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " reference lines\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q13. What items stay the same size no matter the scale of the view?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " line weights\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " annotative components with text\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " model surface patterns\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " hosted components\n</ul>\n", "is_correct": false}]}, {"question": "Q14. When hard-copy printing, what <strong>Print</strong> dialog option allows you to specify that you want sheet 100 of 100 sheets to be at the bottom of the pile, so that sheet 1 of 100 is on the top of the pile?\n", "alternatives": [{"alternative": " Sort Sheets Descending Order\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Reverse Print Order\n", "is_correct": true}, {"alternative": " Last Sheet to Bottom\n", "is_correct": false}, {"alternative": " Set Sheets to Plot in Reverse\n</ul>", "is_correct": false}]}]}